Jewel Catherine N. Lao

+639178632381 | jewellao09@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

A graduate with a double degree in Economics and Marketing Management with experience in events management, public relations, and marketing. Has interned for 10 months under PR, 3 months under Marketing, and 5 months under Sales. Aiming to apply my previous internship experiences, as well as my academics to fulfill this position.

EDUCATION

De La Salle University

Bachelor of Science degree in Applied Economics Major in Industrial Economics, Bachelor of Science degree in Marketing Management

Dean's List: 1st Term, AY 2013-14; 2nd Term, AY 201314; 2nd Term, AY 2014-15

WORK RELATED EXPERIENCE

Sunnies Studios

PR Intern (March 2018 – December 2018)

- Managed the seedings as well as the monthly seeding reports for Sunnies Studios,
 Sunnies Specs, Sunnies Café, and Sunnies Face.
- Handled the Instagram DMs for all brands
- Helped with the preparation and event proper of the Sunnies Face Party launch.
- Managed the Instagram and delivery of wishes for Dear Sunnies Santa.

Call It Spring (Suyen Corporation)

Marketing Intern (September 2017 – November 2017)

- Spearheaded the planning and execution of Call It Spring Retro, which is an event that aimed to launch the 2017 Fall/Winter Collection
- Managed the daily Facebook content of the brand and did routine competition checks Holcim Philippines

Sales Intern (April 2017 – August 2017)

• Mainly handled the Sales Targets of each Sales Officer per Region as well as the Sales Incentive Program of the company

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

DLSU Economics Organization

Executive Vice President for Events (AY 2016 – 2017)

 Managed the Events Department of the organization, which included the following committees: Activities, Academics, and Externals. Helped guide the project heads of all the activities under our organization.

Assistant Vice President for Activities (AY 2015 – 2016)

Headed the following activities: Shirt Selling, Ghost Hunt, Thanksgiving Party,
 Ecolympics: Bowling, and EconOrg Travels: Kapitolyo Food Trip. Shirt Selling went on to win Outstanding Fundraising Activity from the LaSallian Excellence Award.

EXCEL2016

Chairperson for Student Services (AY 2014 – 2015)

 Launched the activity Welcome Shiftees and oversaw the Student Services Announcement.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

I am an adaptable person who will work hard to finish the task with minimal supervision. Being active in my school organizations have also developed my communication skills and my ability to work in teams. I am also willing to learn new skills needed for this position.